Finding Aid for the Rudolph H. Kampmeier, A.B., M.D. Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Rudolph H. Kampmeier, A.B., M.D. Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0235
.84 linear_feet
The materials in the Rudolph H. Kampmeier Collection are arranged in alphabetical order. For economy codes were used to represent cities NY = New York, LA = Los Angelos, N = Nashville, C = Chicago, SL = St. Louis. Brackets were used when a location was not positively known.
- Personal Data
  - Birth - Butler County, Iowa, January 15, 1898
  - Married - Blanche Davis, 1922
  - Daughter - 1927 - Joan Medwedeff
  - Education - Secondary Education, Public Schools of Iowa City, Iowa
    State University of Iowa, Iowa City A.B. degree 1920
    State University of Iowa, College of Medicine M.D. degree 1923
    Alpha Omega Alpha 1922
    Sigma Xi (Associate) 1923
    Alpha Kappa Kappa - Medical Fraternity 1920
    American Board of Internal Medicine Certification 1937
- Military
  - World War I
  - Field Hospital Unit No. 3 - Iowa National Guard (1917-1918)
  - Officers Training (SATC), 1918
  - Medical Officers Reserve - 1st Lieut. University of Michigan General Hospital Unit, 1925-30
  - World War II
  - Office of the Surgeon General of the Army - Clinical
  - Specialist in Nutrition, 1944-46
- Professional Career and Academic Appointments*
  Interneship - St. Mark's Hospital, Salt Lake City, Utah 1923-24
  University of Chicago - Otho Sprague Institute (Fellow) 1925
  University of Michigan Medical School, Ann Arbor
  Junior Instructor in Medicine 1925-27
  Senior Instructor in Medicine 1927-29
  Indiana University School of Medicine, Indianapolis
  Clinical Instructor; Medicine 1929-30
  Louisiana State University Medical School, New Orleans, La.
  Assistant Professor of Medicine 1932-35
  Professor of Clinical Medicine 1935-36
  Vanderbilt University School of Medicine, Nashville, TN.
  Assistant Professor of Medicine 1936-38
  Associate Professor of Medicine 1938-52
  Professor of Medicine 1953-63
  Professor of Medicine, Emeritus 1963-
  Director of Department of Medicine - 1944-46; 1954-55;and 1958-59
  Executive Faculty ' 1958-63
  Director of Course in Syphilis for County Health Officers and Physicians in Public Health Units, and Public Health Nurses 1937-45
  Director of Postgraduate Education 946-66
  - Standing Committees of the Faculty (by School Year)
    on Promotion - 3rd and 4th year 1937-56, Chairman 1957-59
    on Promotion - 1st and 2nd year 1948-58
    on Instruction and Curriculum 1942-56, Chairman 1957-58
    on Admissions 1953-56
    on Postgraduate Instruction 1942-46, Chairman 1947-63
    on Medical Library 1950,1957-58
    on Interneship 1945
    on Rehabilitation 1957-58
    Joint Committee on Interneship, Exec. Faculty and Hospital Committee 1951-56, Chairman 1957-58
    V.A. Dean's Committee 1946-57
    *Dates refer to years of appointment as listed in school catalogues, etc., for the academic years respectively and not as "inclusive."
  - Hospital Appointments
    Methodist Episcopal Hospital, Indianapolis, Ind.
    Associate attending 1929- 30
    Parkview Hospital, Pueblo, Colo. Visiting Physician 1930- 32
    Charity Hospital of New Orleans, Visiting Physician 1932-36
    Vanderbilt University Hospital
    Physician-In-Chief 1958
    Associate Visiting Physician 1936-40
    Visiting Physician 1940- 63
    Chief of Medical Clinic 1947-61
    Committees of the Hospital Staff
    Hospital Committee of Medical Faculty 1941- 49
    Executive Committee 1958
    Committee on Credentials 1958
    Subcommittee on Outpatient Service 1936-43, Chairman 1944-58
    Subcommittee on Social Service 1941-42, Chairman 1943-46
    Subcommittee on Nursing Service 1947- 49
    Committee on Medical Records Chairman 1948- 58
    Committee on Pharmacy 1951-54
    Committee on Rehabilitation Service Chairman 1962
    Director, Office of Vocational Rehabilitation at V.U.H. 1957-66
    Central State1 Psychiatric Hospital
    Medical Consultant 1942- 70
    Chief of the Medical Service 1971-78
    Thayer Veterans Administration Hospital - Consultant 1947-
    Nashville General Hospital, Chief of Medical Service 1953-54
    Director Medical Education, Saint Thomas Hospital 1960-65
    Active Staff, Saint Thomas Hospital 1960-73
    Consulting Staff, Saint Thomas Hospital 1973-
    Active Staff, Park View Hospital 1965-77
    Honorary Staff, Park View Hospital 1977-
  - Membership in Professional Organizations
    American Medical Association 1924 Veteran 1969
    Carbon County Medical Society 1924
    Utah State Medical Association 1924
    Washtenaw County Medical Society 1925
    Michigan State Medical Society 1925
    Pueblo County Medical Society 1930
    Colorado Medical Society 1930
    Orleans Parish Medical Society 1932
    Louisiana State Medical Society 1932
    Nashville Academy of Medicine and Davidson County Medical
    Society - 1936 Veteran - 1969
    Tennessee Medical Association 1936 Veteran 1969
    American College of Physicians (Life Member)
    Associate 1927
    Fellow 1927
    Master 1972
    Southern Medical Association 1935 Life Member 1961
    American Clinical and Climatological Association 1937 Emeritus 1958
    Association of American Physicins 1948 Emeritus 1963
    Association of American Medical Colleges 1955 Emeritus 1963
    Southern Society for Clinical Research (Honorary) Member of the Founding Group of five 1946
    Nashville Society of Internal Medicine (one of founders and first President) 1948
    Royal College of Physicians of London (Fellow) 1969
    Royal College of Physicians of Ireland (Honorary Fellow) 1968
    American Society of Internal Medicine 1956 Retired 1969
    Southeastern Clinical Club 1953-
    American Venereal Disease Association 1970-
  - Nashville Academy of Medicine and Davidson County Medical Society
    President Elect 1950
    President 1951
    Board of Directors 1950-54 Chairman 1952-53
    Committees
    on Postgraduate Programs 1948-53
    on Improvement of Nashville as a Medical Center 1949
    on Integration of House Staffs of Nashville’s Hospitals 1950-52
    on News Media and Information 1959-64
    on Program 1967-70
  - Tennessee Medical Association
    Secretary-Editor 1950-1971
    Board of Trustees (Ex-officio) 1950-57
    Board of Trustees 1957-66
    President Elect 1963-64
    President 1964-65
    on Scientific Work - Chairman 1950-63
    on Scientific Work and Post-
    graduate Education Chairman 1964-66 Member 1967-70
    on Legislative and Public Policy (Ex-officio) 1950-71
    on Prepaid Insurance
    Exec. Committee 1959-55
    Exec. Committee (Ex-officio) 1956-69
    on Public Service (Exec. Comm.) 1956-71
    on Continuing Education-Chairman 1968-70 Member 1971-75
    on Study Postgraduate Education 1955
    on Liaison to Department of Public Welfare - Chairman 1953-54 Member 1955
    on Liaison to Public Health Council 1955-56
    on TMA-Headquarters Building 1955-57
    on Membership Expansion 1954
    on Grievance 1965-66
    on Mediation - Chairman 1967
    on State Utilization 1966-69
  - American Medical Association
    Committee on Preparation for General Practice 1957-59
    Section on Internal Medicine - Secretary 1956-59 Chairman 1959-60
    National Congress on Mental Health -1961 -Chairman, Section on Continuing Education of Physicians
    Residency Review Committee for Internal Medicine (Council on Medical Education) 1963-69
    Awards Committee - Scientific Exhibits 1963-70 Chairman 1971
    Consulting Editor (JAMA) on V.D. upon occasion 1965-
    Department of Continuing Education - Site Surveyor upon occasion 1968-
    Section on Nutrition Information (field trips) 1966-67
  - American College of Physicians
    Governor for Tennessee 1954-61
    Regent 1961-67; 1968-71
    President-Elect, 1966-67
    President 1967-68 (combined meeting ACR-RCP(L) Sir Max Rosenheim, president)
    Exec. Committee - Board of Regents 1966-69
    on Postgraduate Courses 1954-58 Chairman 1959-61
    on Credentials 1957-64
    on Membership 1962-66
    on Constitution and By-laws 1962-66
    on International Medical Activities 1962-66
    on Nominations 1963-64 Chairman 1964-65
    on Finance and Budgets 1964-68
    on Scientific Program 1966-68
    on Consulting, Scientific Program 1967-70
    on Awards, Masterships, Honorary and Corresponding Fellows 1957-58; 1965 Chairman 1969-71
    Representative of ACP -
    with APA Task Force Chairman 1964-67
    Council of Medical Specialty Societies 1967-68
    Medical Intersociety Council 1967-68
    Committee on Training in Mammography and Diseases of the Breast. Commission on Education, American College of Radiology 1967-74
    Conference, Commission on Drug Safety 1963
    National Symposium - V.D. Control (ANA - USPHS) 1965
    White House Conference on Food, Nutrition and Health 1969
    National Commission on Venereal Disease 1970-71
    Postgraduate Seminars in Internal Medicine - Vanderbilt University School of Medicine - 1953 and 1956 - Co-directors, R.H. Kampmeier, Hugh J. Morgan
    Symposium on Food Standards (NRC and AMA Council on Nutrition) 1969
  - Southern Medical Association
    First Vice President 1962-63
    President-Elect 1963-64
    Council - Exec. Committee 1963-65
    Board of Trustees 1965-71
    Committees -
    on Publications (Ex-officio) 1956-78
    on Scientific Exhibits,Chairman 1960-72
    on Journal Advertising 1961-78
    On History, Chairman 1965-78
  - Association of American Medical Colleges
    on Medical Care Plans (appointed) 1955
    on Continuing Education (appointed) 1959
    Clinical Institute 1958
  - American Venereal Disease Association
    Board of Directors 1971-74 (Ex-officio) 1975-76
  - American Social Health Association
    Venereal Disease Research Fund Advisory Group 1975-1981
  - Federal Government
    Office of Scientific Research and Development, Committee on Medical Research, Responsible Investigator, Study on Penicillin in Syphilis 1943-49
    Surgeon-General’s Office of the Army in Nutrition
    K-Ration Trials 1944
    Nutrition Survey’s Germany, American Zone and Berlin 1945
    Interdepartmental Committee on Nutrition for National Defense
    Ecuador Survey - Deputy Director and Clinician 1960
    Republic of Lebanon - Clinician 1961
    Hashemite Kingdom of Jordan - Clinician 1962
    Advisory Committee on Cancer Control (HEW) 1963-67
    Consultant 1967-70
    Consultant on Venereal Disease 1964-75
    Consultant Nome (Alaska) Rehabilitation Demonstration Project (OVR) 1961-64
    Grant Review Committee - Region IV Health Services Development Project 1968-71
    Regional Medical Program (Mid-South) Advisory Committee 1967-71 (inclusive)
    National Commission on Venereal Disease 1971-72
    Participant in:
    Conference on Venereal Disease Control - USPHS 1963
    Institute on Rehabilitation Teaching in Medicine (HEW) 1958
    World Forum on Syphilis and Other Treponematoses 1962
    Southeast Regional Institute on Public Health and Rehabilitation 1963
    Venereal Disease Seminar (Houston) USPHS 1964
    Venreal Disease Seminar (Pan American Health Organization) 1965
  - State of Tennessee
    Department of Mental Health - Committee on Problems of Aged 1955-56
    Governor’s Committee on Aging 1960-64
    Planning Committee for State White House Conference 1959
    White House Conference 1961
    Commission on Aging, Chairman Advisory Committee 1970-78
    White House Conference on Aging 1971
  - Community Activities
    Senior Citizens, Inc.
    Research Committee 1957-66
    Board of Directors 1957-66 Chairman 1960-62
    Mayor’s Committee on Housing for the Aged 1960-68
    Bill Wilkerson Hearing and Speech Center
    Board of Directors 1966-81 Exec. Committee 1969-77
    Secretary 1970-76
    Chamber of Commerce Health and Hospital Committee 1959-62
    Health and Hospital Planning Council Exec. Committee 1963-69
    Director of Health Services for Civil Defense (Nashville-Davidson County) 1957
  - Private Practice
    Castle Cate, Utah (mining camp) 1924
    Pueblo, Colorado (group practice) 1930-32
  - Medical Literature
    Editorships
    American Practitioner and Digest of Treatment
    Assistant Editor 1946-58
    Editor 1958-62
    Journal of Tennessee Medical Association (inclusive) 1950-71
    Southern Medical Journal 1954-72
    Southern Medical Bulletin 1961-71
    Southern Medicine 1972-78
    Journal of the American Venereal Disease Association 1974-76
  - Books
    - Essentials of Syphilology, J.B. Lippincott Company, Philadelphia, 1943 Reprint, 1944. (English Edition: Blackwell’s, London; Spanish Translation, Salvat Editores, Barcelona-Buenos Aires)
    - Physical Examination in Health and Disease, F.A. Davis Co. Philadelphia, 1950; 2nd Edition 1957 (pirated reprint in Taiwan, 1961); 3rd Edition 1964. (Spanish Translation, Paz Montalvo, 1970); 4th Edition (with Blake) 1970; Philippine Edition, 1977).
    - Recollections: The Department of Medicine, Vanderbilt University, 1980
    - History of the Tennessee Medical Association, (1930-1980) 1980
  - Bibliography
    Published papers
    Chapters in text books 3
    Editorials - American Practitioner 10
    Editorials - J. Tennessee Medical Association 317
    Editorials - Southern Medical J. 212
    Editorials - Southern Medical Bull. 79
  - Recognition
    American Men of Science 1949
    Who's Who in America 1948
    The Blue Book 1970
    Physician of the Year, Tennessee Medical Association 1958
    Who's Who in the World 1980
    "Physician of the Year" - Tennessee Medical Association 1958
    Symposium on Syphilis and Other Venereal Diseases upon occasion of Retirement - (Vanderbilt University Number. 1963
    Medical Clinics of North America 48 (no. 3) May 1964).
    Distinguished Service Award, Southern Medical Association 1969
    Fellow Royal College of Physicians. (London) 1968
    Fellow Royal College of Physicians, Honorary (Ireland) 1968
    The State of Tennessee Certification of Appreciation in recognition of Dedication to the Service of Others, and Certificate of Congratulations in recognition of being an Outstanding Older American from Tennessee. 1971
    Mastership, American College of Physicians 1972
    The Alfred Stengel Award of the American C. of Physicians 1973
    The Roaman E. and Thomas G. Sheen Award, American Medical Association 1975
    The Ralph 0. Claypoole Sr. Memorial Award 1981
    The Thomas H. Parran Award, American Venereal Disease Ass. 1975
    The William Freeman Snow Award, American Social Health Association 1979
    Recognition (plaque) Tennessee Academy of Family Physicians 1980
    Southern Society Medical Research Founder's Medal 1981
    President's Award - Nashville Academy of Medicine 1983
  - Miscellaneous Activities
    Visiting Professor of Medicine, University of Puerto Rico 1953
    Conference on Cardiovascular Training Grant Directors 1955
    Physician-in-Chief- Pro tempore, Cleveland Clinic 1955
    RCA-Medical Radio System - Editorial Board 1960-61
    Vanderbilt University Long Range Planning Committee Chairman Committee on University and Public 1963
    National Formulary, Advisory Committee on Admissions 1965-70
    Joint Study Committee on Continuing Education, AMA, AAMC and 6 other sponsors 1961-62
    Conference on Principles of Rehabilitation on Teaching
    Undergraduate Medical Students - New York Academy of Science 1966
    Middle Tennessee Heart Association, Board of Directors 1952-55
    Medical Advisory Committee, 1951-54
    Xth International Cancer Congress 1970
    University of Tenenssee, Nursing Home Administrators Educational Program 1971-72
    The Malcolm C. Grow Memorial Lecture, Society of Air Force Physicians 1969
    The John Archinard Lecture, Oshsner Clinic, New Orleans 1969
    The William S. Middleton Lecture, Regional Meeting of ACP and ASIM, Wisconsin 1970
    Virgil P. Sydenstricker Lecture, University of Georgia 1967
    American Board of Internal Medicine - Guest Examiner 1955-58; 1961-62
    National Board of Medical Examiners - Associate Chief Examiner Subsidiary Board 1948-54
    National Association of Retail Druggists - Advisory Committee on Venereal Diseases. 1972-75
  - (Box 1)
    Playbills — Programs
    All the Way Home by Tad Mosel based on novel A Death In the Family by James Agee, 1961 Belasco Theatre NY
    The American College of Physicians Annual Banquet featuring Bob Hope, April 19, 1956 Biltmore Hotel LA
    Amphitryon 38, a comedy by Jean Giraudoux, March 7, 1939 Ryman Auditorium N
    Annie Get Your Gun, Rodgers and Hammerstein production with music and lyrics by Irving Berlin, starring Billie Worth, March 21 & 22, 1949 Ryman Auditorium N
    Auntie Mame, a new comedy by Jerome Lawrence & Robert E. Lee, based on the novel by Patrick Dennis, starring Sylvia Sidney, Tennessee Theatre N
    Babes in Arms by George Oppenheimer music by Richard Rogers and lyrics by Lorenz Hart, May 1961 Theatre Nashville N
    Bad Seed starring Nancy Kelly Week of June 3, 1956 Harris Theatre C
    Ballets Espagnols, choreograped and directed by Teresa and Luisillo,1954-55 Community Concert Association NY
    Born Yesterday by Garson Kanin 1950-51 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Boy Friend, a new musical comedy of the 1920’s by Sandy Wilson, April 17-25, 1959 Theatre Nashville N
    Brigadoon, a musical play in 2 acts by Alan Jay Lerner, April 13-April 23, 1960 New Theatre Nashville N
    Bus Stop by William Inge, February 21- March 2, 1957 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Caine Mutiny Court Martial by Herman Wouk, February 23-March 3, 1956 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Camelot starring Richard Burton and Julie Andrews, production staged by Moss Hart, December 3, 1960 Majestic Theatre NY
    Camille by Alexandre Dumas Fils starring Carmen Mathews, 1948-49 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Cat On A Hot Tin Roof, by Tennessee Williams, November 5-15, 1958 Circle Theatre N
    The Cave Dwellers, William Saroyan January 18-27, 1962 Theatre Nashville N
    Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra presented by the comunity Concert Association,, February 26, 1952 N
    The Columbus Pilgrimage to Ante Bellum Homes, co-sponsored by the Columbus Chamber of Commerce, March 26-April 3, 1960 Columbus, Mississippi
    Don Cossack, the original chorus & dancers, directed by Serge Jaroff, Thursday January 15 War Memorial Auditorium N
    The Curious - Savage by John Patrick starring Zasu Pitts, November 1960 Theatre Nashville N
    Cyrano de Bergerac, the Brian Hooker version of Edmond Rostand's immortal play Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Danced Theatre, presented by the Community Concert Association with Ruth Mata and Eugene Hari and company, 1952-1953 Community Concert Association NY
    The Dark at the Top of the Stairs by William Inge, March 22-31,1962 Theatre Nashville N
    Death of A Salesman, by Arthur Miller April 9-18, 1953 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Henri Deering, Pianist, presented by the Community Concert Association [N]
    Detective Story by Sidney Kingsley 1951 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Dial M for Murder by Frederick Knott, December 1-10, 1955 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Fallen Angels, a comedy in 3 acts, by Noel Coward, 1960 New Theatre Nashville N
    Arthur Fiedler and the Boston Pops Orchestra presented by the Community Concert Association, 1954-55 and 1956-57 [N]
    Finian's Rainbow, a musical fantasy, book by E.Y. Harburg and Fred Saidy June 11-23, 1950 Nashville Community Playhouse [N]
    Flower Drum Song, a Rodgers & Hammerstein production, starring Elaine Dunn, October 31-November 12, 1960 American Theatre SL
    The Fourposter by Jan de Hartog, October 14-23, 1955 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Gentlemen prefer Blondes by Anita Loos and Joseph Fields, May 19-29, 1954 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Glass Menagerie by Tennessee Williams, January 28-February 4, 1948 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Goodbye My Fancy by Fay Kanin, March 28-April 7, 1951 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Great Waltz by Moss Hart, November 19, 1936 Ryman Auditorium N
    Half a Sixpence by H.G. Wells' Kipps, starring Tommy Steele, June 1965 Broadhurst Theatre NY
    Happy Birthday, a comedy in two acts, by Anita Loos, November 16-26, 1949 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Hellz a Poppin, presented by Olsen & Johnson, starring Jay C. Flippen and Happy Felton, October 5, 1941 Winter Garden NY
    Hello Dolly, starring Ginger Rogers April 1966 St. James Theatre NY
    Nicole Henriot, pianist, presented by the Community Concert Association, 1951-52 [N]
    The Indoor Sport by Jack B. Perry, April 22-May 1, 1954 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Inherit The Wind by Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee
    March 19, 1956’ starring Paul Muni National Theatre NY
    Ed Begley and Tony Randall' January 10-18, 1958 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Julius Caesar by William Shakespeare, January, 1961 Theatre Nashville N
    Kind Lady by Edward Chodorov, February 27-March 8, 1952 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    King of Hearts by Jean Kerr and Eleanor Brooke, October 13-22, 1955 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Lady Audley's Secret, directed by Laverne Seeman, February 9-March 30, 1968 The First Theatre Pacific Grove, CA
    Lady in the Dark by Moss Hart, starring Gertrude Lawrence, October 13, 1941 Alvin Theatre NY
    Life with Father by Russel Crouse and Howard Lindsay, March 5-14, 1953 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Lotte Lehmann, leading Soprano Metropolitan Opera Ass'n, presented by the Community Concert Association [N]
    Light Up The Sky by Moss Hart, May 21-30, 1953 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Look Back In Anger by John Osborne, March 16-26, 1960 New Theatre Nashville N
    Look Homeward, Angel by Ketti Frings April, 1961 Theatre Nashville N
    Luv by Murray Schisgal, starring Eli Wallach, Anne Jackson and Alan Arkin, June 1965 Booth Theatre NY
    Macbeth by William Shakespeare, April 25- May 4, 1949 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    MAdame Butterfly, music by Giacomo Puccini 1962 Theatre Nashville N
    The Madwoman of Chaillot by Jean Giraudoux January 1-February 10, 1951 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Man and Superman by George Bernard Shaw December 6-16, 1950 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Master of Ballantrae by Robert Louis Stevenson, starring Walker Whiteside, January 13, 1935 Tulane Theatre Louisiana
    The Minneapolis Orchestra, conductor Antal Dorati, 1955-56 [N]
  - (Box 2)
    Mister Roberts by Thomas Heggen and Josh Logan, December 2-11, 1954 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Moon is Blue by F. Hugh Herbert, a delightfully sophisticated comedy of young love, December 3-12, 1953 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Moulin Rouge, Frank Senne's Hollywood, CA
    The Music Man, starring Forrest Tucker April 19, 1959 Shubert theatre Chicago
    My Fair Lady, production staged by
    Moss Hart, adapted from Bernard Shaw's
    Pygmalion
    March 13, 1961’ starring Michael Allinson and Margot Moser Mark He1linger Theatre N
    October 5, 1958’ starring Michael Evans and Anne Rogers Shubert Theatre Chicago
    My Sister Eileen, a new play by Joseph Fields and Jerome Chodorov, presented by Max Gordon, October 13, 1941 Biltmore Theatre NY
    Nashville Symphony Orchestra, conductor Guy Taylor
    February 22, 1955 War Mémorial Auditorium N
    December 11 Vanderbilt Memorial Gymnasium N
    Night Must Fall by Emlyn Williams April 19-22, 1939 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Of Mice and Men by John Steinbeck, March 21-26, 1955 Nashville Community N
    Oliver, book, music and lyrics by Lionel Bart starring Judy Bruce and Robin Ramsay, directed by Peter Coe, March 1965 Shubert Theatre Chicago
    On Borrowed Time by Paul Osborn, February 7’12, 1955 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    One Of The Family by Kenneth Webb, February 7, 1927 Bonstelle Playhouse Detroit